Guide to the Time Inc. Sports Illustrated Publishing and Business Records 1950s-1993 MS 3009-RG 35
New-York Historical Society
- Series V. Merchandising Working File, 1953-1957; 2.5 Linear feet in 3 record cartons and 1 flat box
  - Woodward and Lothrop, 1954 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 29)
  - Woodward Stores: Canada, 1954 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 30)
  - World Series Scouting Reports, 1955 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 31)
  - Wulff, Maggie: Television Show, 1954 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 32)
  - Yachting Kit, 1955 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 33)
  - Young & Rubicam, Inc., 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 4143, Folder 34)
- Series VI. Market Research Studies, 1981-1987; 1.5 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
  The Market Research Studies all focus on Sports Illustrated (SI) or the women's sports magazine Time Inc. published for a year as a trial run. A note in the Redesign Study folder transfers the study to "Susan," possibly SI Research Director Susan Alexander. Most or all studies were conducted by Beta Research Corp.
  Organized alphabetically with arrangement imposed by the archivist.
  - Redesign Study, 1987 March (Offsite-box 4150, Folder 1)
  - Sports Opinion Study, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 4150, Folder 2-11)
  - Subscriber Study, 1981 (Offsite-box 4150, Folder 12)
  - Women's Sports & Fitness: Renewal Intent Study, 1987 (Offsite-box 4151, Folder 1-6)
  - Women's Sports & Fitness: Subscriber Study, 1987 (Offsite-box 4151, Folder 7-9)